gamemaps.com 2019-06-17

# Privacy Policy - GameMaps

∅ Cookies for this site are not being saved. Make sure cookies for this site are not blocked by your browser or a firewall. ∅ 

Privacy Policy

* Google ReCaptcha Policy

  * You acknowledge and understand that the reCAPTCHA API works by collecting hardware and software information, such as device and application data, and sending these data to Google for analysis. The information collected in connection with your use of the service will be used for improving reCAPTCHA and for general security purposes. It will not be used for personalized advertising by Google. Pursuant to Section 3(d) of the Google APIs Terms of Service, you agree that if you use the APIs that it is your responsibility to provide any necessary notices or consents for the collection and sharing of this data with Google. For users in the European Union, you and your API Client(s) must comply with the EU User Consent Policy currently located at http://www.google.com/about/company/user-consent-policy.html.

* Advertisements

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site.
  * We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, visit your google account settings.

* Our Commitment To Privacy

  * Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested. 

* The way we use information

  * We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties. Your personal information (name, last, email, password) is never visible or given to any other parties.
  * We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website and to share with advertisers. For example, we may tell an advertiser that X number of individuals visited a certain area on our website, or that Y number of men and Z number of women filled out our registration form, but we would not disclose anything that could be used to identify those individuals.
  * Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses. 

* Our Commitment To Data Security

  * To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. 

* Our Commitment To Children's Privacy

  * Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13. 

* How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information

  * You can correct software and user factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error.
  * To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections. 

* How To Contact Us

  * Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please contact us.
